[Music] Have you
ever thought what you will become when you grow old When you grow old I don't
[Music]
No I just want to be a very happy go
lucky and a free senior citizen So what I do is
for my village I want to go back to work Mujhe logon ki prakesh sunke unko
help karna hai
Something related to education I should be a
good human being in the age of my life I want to go back
to my roots again later and
I want to do some surveys over there I don't know because
I take life as it comes So when I grow old I start
teaching and when I grow old I do astrology I have a lot
of regrets in my life if I am not able to
play the piano and speak
flute Japanese Why do I
visualize Tokyo 2050 somewhere I want to
grow up I won't want to do anything Nothing nothing to do
[Music]
You liked my color I liked yours
So I like bras very much
[Music]
What will you become when you grow old